<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Compliment</string>
    <string name="title_select_days">Select Days of the Week</string>
    <string name="title_select_time">Select Time</string>
    <string name="message_no_selected_day">Please select at least one day</string>
    <string name="compliment_copied">compliment copied</string>
    <string name="permission_needed">Permission Needed</string>
    <string name="text_permission_notifications">This permission is required for notifications. Please enable it in the app settings.</string>
    <string name="text_permission_exact_alarm">Permission is required to enable accurate alarms. You can enable it in the software.</string>
    <string name="go_settings">Go to Settings</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="title_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_reminders">Reminders</string>
    <string name="title_compliments">Compliments</string>
    <string name="enable_dark_theme">Enable dark theme</string>
    <string name="enable_exact_notification_time">Enable exact notification time</string>
    <string name="for_women">Compliments for women</string>
    <string name="for_men">Compliments for men</string>
    <string name="new_schedule">New reminder</string>
    <string name="edit_schedule">Edit reminder</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="lang_russian">Russian</string>
    <string name="lang_english">English</string>
    <string name="title_nice_day">It\'s a great day to say kind words!</string>
    <string name="get_compliment">Get a compliment</string>
    <string name="empty_reminders">This is empty for now, create a new reminder</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="every_day">Every day</string>

    <string-array name="compliments_women">
        <item>You look absolutely stunning today!</item>
        <item>Your smile lights up the world!</item>
        <item>You are incredibly talented!</item>
        <item>It’s always a pleasure to talk to you!</item>
        <item>Your kindness makes the world a better place!</item>
        <item>You have amazing strength!</item>
        <item>You inspire everyone around you!</item>
        <item>Being with you makes me want to be better!</item>
        <item>You make the world brighter!</item>
        <item>You know how to support in tough moments!</item>
        <item>Your energy is so uplifting!</item>
        <item>You always know how to cheer people up!</item>
        <item>You are a true star!</item>
        <item>Your style is amazing!</item>
        <item>You have an exceptional sense of humor!</item>
        <item>Being with you makes me laugh until I cry!</item>
        <item>You are unique and one of a kind!</item>
        <item>You are so caring and attentive!</item>
        <item>Your kindness knows no bounds!</item>
        <item>You are the perfect example of feminine strength and beauty!</item>
        <item>You light up everything around you just by being there!</item>
        <item>Your eyes shine like stars!</item>
        <item>Your confidence is inspiring!</item>
        <item>You are the embodiment of tenderness and beauty!</item>
        <item>You are a true muse to all of us!</item>
        <item>Your smile can warm even the coldest day!</item>
        <item>With you, any task feels easy!</item>
        <item>Your presence makes the world a better place!</item>
        <item>You are the epitome of elegance and grace!</item>
        <item>Your ideas are always so creative and unique!</item>
        <item>You inspire greatness in others!</item>
        <item>You are beautiful not only on the outside but on the inside too!</item>
        <item>You are full of surprises and mysteries!</item>
        <item>You harmoniously combine strength and tenderness!</item>
        <item>You have a unique ability to find positivity in any situation!</item>
        <item>Being with you is always interesting and fun!</item>
        <item>You bring so much joy into this world!</item>
        <item>You are a true role model!</item>
        <item>You are a true queen!</item>
        <item>Your sense of style is impeccable!</item>
        <item>You always see the best in people!</item>
        <item>You are incredibly wise and insightful!</item>
        <item>You are a wonderful listener and conversationalist!</item>
        <item>You inspire others to act in the best way possible!</item>
        <item>You turn ordinary moments into something magical!</item>
        <item>You always bring light to any group you’re in!</item>
        <item>You make the world cozier and warmer!</item>
        <item>You see the beauty in the little things!</item>
        <item>With you, every event becomes a celebration!</item>
        <item>You have incredible magnetism!</item>
        <item>You are the embodiment of harmony and coziness!</item>
        <item>Being with you is easy and pleasant!</item>
        <item>Your bravery is inspiring!</item>
        <item>You possess a special grace!</item>
        <item>Your eyes are so expressive!</item>
        <item>You are always so charming!</item>
        <item>You know how to create comfort around you!</item>
        <item>You are the sweetest person I know!</item>
        <item>Your voice is like music to the ears!</item>
        <item>You have a strong and kind heart!</item>
        <item>Your love for life is inspiring!</item>
        <item>With you, I feel truly alive!</item>
        <item>You find joy in the little things!</item>
        <item>You are a true miracle!</item>
        <item>You radiate so much warmth!</item>
        <item>You are a true romantic!</item>
        <item>Your smile brightens my world!</item>
        <item>You deserve only the best in life!</item>
        <item>You fill the world with light!</item>
        <item>You make my days brighter!</item>
        <item>You always find joy in every day!</item>
        <item>You are an inspiration!</item>
        <item>You are a source of light and joy!</item>
        <item>With you, I feel happy!</item>
        <item>You can make any day better with just one look!</item>
        <item>You have the power to change the world for the better!</item>
        <item>You bring so much happiness to everyone around you!</item>
        <item>You carry an immense inner strength within you!</item>
        <item>Your smile makes everything around you brighter!</item>
        <item>Every moment with you is unique!</item>
        <item>You are the epitome of coziness and warmth!</item>
        <item>You give me inspiration!</item>
        <item>You are full of surprises and unexpected delights!</item>
        <item>You make me happier every day!</item>
        <item>You are an amazing person!</item>
        <item>You are my muse!</item>
        <item>You are like a ray of sunshine on a cloudy day!</item>
        <item>You are full of incredible strength and grace!</item>
        <item>You always find a way out of any situation!</item>
        <item>You bring so much happiness into this world!</item>
        <item>You have true feminine wisdom!</item>
        <item>You always look stylish and fashionable!</item>
        <item>You make the world a little bit better!</item>
        <item>You are always caring and attentive!</item>
        <item>You radiate confidence!</item>
        <item>You are my pride and joy!</item>
        <item>You light up my life with your smile!</item>
        <item>You give my life meaning!</item>
        <item>Every day with you is special!</item>
        <item>You are a true diamond that shines in the dark!</item>
        <item>You possess a unique charm!</item>
        <item>Your passion for life is inspiring!</item>
        <item>You always find the right words!</item>
        <item>You make me feel important!</item>
        <item>You have a fine sense of tact!</item>
        <item>With you, the world feels calmer!</item>
        <item>You turn challenges into opportunities!</item>
        <item>You are my brightest star!</item>
        <item>Your love for people is impressive!</item>
        <item>You always understand me without words!</item>
        <item>You make my life fuller!</item>
        <item>You bring me joy with every word you say!</item>
        <item>You always support me when I need it!</item>
        <item>You have exquisite taste!</item>
        <item>You notice the beauty even in ordinary things!</item>
        <item>You add magic to every moment!</item>
        <item>With you, I can truly be myself!</item>
        <item>You are a true rarity in this world!</item>
        <item>You make every meeting unforgettable!</item>
        <item>You know how to give warmth just because!</item>
        <item>Your generosity of spirit is amazing!</item>
        <item>You always find the strength for a new victory!</item>
        <item>You make the world better just by being here!</item>
        <item>You inspire me to become better!</item>
        <item>You are so extraordinary and interesting!</item>
        <item>Every day with you is filled with meaning!</item>
        <item>You are truly a unique person!</item>
        <item>You know how to listen and understand!</item>
        <item>You are like a sunbeam on a cloudy day!</item>
        <item>You inspire me to be braver!</item>
        <item>You are like music for the soul!</item>
        <item>You bring harmony to my life!</item>
        <item>Your advice is always so wise and helpful!</item>
        <item>You are a true gift from fate!</item>
        <item>Your tenderness and strength are a unique combination!</item>
        <item>Being with you is always easy and pleasant!</item>
        <item>You always find the best in every person!</item>
        <item>You are like a cozy place that I always want to return to!</item>
        <item>You always know how to support!</item>
        <item>You are so sweet and caring!</item>
        <item>You bring happiness into the lives of everyone around you!</item>
        <item>You are an amazing creation of nature!</item>
        <item>You are a true beauty!</item>
        <item>You deserve only the best!</item>
        <item>You always look incredible!</item>
        <item>You radiate warmth and care!</item>
        <item>You are truly a heroine in my life!</item>
        <item>You are the embodiment of perfection!</item>
        <item>You are amazing: your sincerity and strength of character make every moment spent with you awe-inspiring.</item>
        <item>You are like a bright star that lights up the darkest path and helps believe in the best.</item>
        <item>When you are near, I feel that I can overcome any difficulties — your faith in me lifts me up!</item>
        <item>Your kindness knows no bounds, and that makes you truly unique!</item>
        <item>You notice the little things that most would miss, and that quality of yours makes the world special.</item>
        <item>Every conversation with you is like a real adventure — you perceive everything around you so subtly and wisely!</item>
        <item>You bring harmony and peace wherever you go, like a breath of fresh air in the hustle of the day.</item>
        <item>You have a magical ability to listen — with you, I feel heard and understood like never before.</item>
        <item>Each of your smiles lights up the day and seems to invite into a world full of warmth and sincerity.</item>
        <item>With you, I feel more alive, inspired, and full of ideas — your energy is contagious to everyone around.</item>
        <item>Your strength and tenderness blend so harmoniously that it sometimes feels like you are a work of art.</item>
        <item>You can show beauty even in the simplest things, making me look at the world differently.</item>
        <item>You are one of those people with whom it\'s enough to just be silent and enjoy the moment.</item>
        <item>You create comfort wherever you are, and that is a rare and beautiful quality.</item>
        <item>Every word you say is filled with kindness and warmth, and I always feel better after talking to you.</item>
        <item>You are the embodiment of harmony and tenderness, and looking at you, I want to be kinder and more attentive to the world.</item>
        <item>Your confidence inspires me to become better and reach new heights.</item>
        <item>You bring a sense of coziness and comfort into my life that cannot be faked — it\'s your true gift.</item>
        <item>Your support is invaluable to me: you are like a bridge that always leads to the right decision.</item>
        <item>You are amazingly wise, and I am always curious to know your perspective on any situation — it\'s full of insights.</item>
        <item>When I\'m with you, I always feel sincerity and purity, which are so lacking in the modern world.</item>
        <item>You know how to inspire, and that inspiration comes from the heart — your sincerity always wins people over.</item>
        <item>You are like a spring sunbeam, bringing warmth and hope even on the gloomiest days.</item>
        <item>With you, time flies unnoticed, because every minute is filled with sincerity and joy.</item>
        <item>You have a special talent for creating real connections with people, and that is priceless.</item>
        <item>Your kindness and care make the world a better place, and I am proud to know you.</item>
        <item>You are one of those people who leave a mark on hearts — your soul is incredibly beautiful.</item>
        <item>With you, I can talk about anything, and I always feel that our connection is special.</item>
        <item>You are the embodiment of femininity and wisdom, and I often wonder how you manage to combine everything so harmoniously.</item>
        <item>You bring so much meaning and joy into my life that every day spent with you becomes a celebration.</item>
        <item>Your smile is like the sun after rain, always bringing warmth and light.</item>
        <item>You have an incredible ability to create a world around you full of peace and comfort.</item>
        <item>Your energy charges others with positivity, and I never get tired of being around you.</item>
        <item>You know how to see light in the simplest things, and that makes me believe in miracles.</item>
        <item>You are an inspiration to many, and I am happy that you are in my life.</item>
        <item>Your faith in the best always inspires me to overcome all difficulties and keep moving forward.</item>
        <item>You know how to give joy so sincerely that it\'s impossible not to notice.</item>
        <item>You remind me that everything is possible in this world if you keep the faith and stay true to yourself.</item>
        <item>Your generosity of soul has no limits, and I cherish every moment spent with you.</item>
        <item>You are the kind of person who inspires belief in good and light in this world.</item>
        <item>Your eyes shine like stars, and every glance fills the soul with warmth and tranquility.</item>
        <item>You have a special gift of being truly honest and open — that is a rare quality.</item>
        <item>With you, I can dream about anything and not fear that my dreams won’t come true.</item>
        <item>You are like a guiding star, always leading me to the brightest path.</item>
        <item>You are so beautiful not only on the outside but also on the inside, and that makes you truly amazing.</item>
        <item>Your words always support and inspire, and that is a gift not given to everyone.</item>
        <item>You create an atmosphere of warmth and coziness even in the most mundane situations.</item>
        <item>You are always sincere and open, and I feel truly happy being with you.</item>
        <item>You know how to support and inspire, even when everything around seems complicated and confusing.</item>
        <item>You are the brightest person I know, and that fills my life with meaning and joy.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="compliments_men">
        <item>You\'re handsome!</item>
        <item>You\'re a real man!</item>
        <item>You\'re amazing!</item>
        <item>You\'re awesome!</item>
        <item>You look great!</item>
        <item>You\'re a real hero!</item>
        <item>You\'re just cool!</item>
        <item>You\'re the best!</item>
        <item>You\'re strong and confident!</item>
        <item>You\'re simply stunning!</item>
        <item>You\'re a smart one!</item>
        <item>You\'re chic!</item>
        <item>You\'re fire!</item>
        <item>You\'re the king!</item>
        <item>You\'re a great guy!</item>
        <item>You\'re my hero!</item>
        <item>You\'re just class!</item>
        <item>You\'re a handsome guy!</item>
        <item>You\'re simply fantastic!</item>
        <item>You have a strength that inspires.</item>
        <item>Your confidence makes this world better.</item>
        <item>With you, I can always count on support.</item>
        <item>You inspire great deeds.</item>
        <item>Your kindness makes you truly strong.</item>
        <item>You know how to find a way out of any situation.</item>
        <item>Your strength lies in calmness and confidence.</item>
        <item>You bring confidence and light to any moment.</item>
        <item>With you, it\'s always interesting and easy.</item>
        <item>You\'re a role model.</item>
        <item>Your care for others knows no bounds.</item>
        <item>You always remain true to yourself.</item>
        <item>Your words are always full of meaning and strength.</item>
        <item>With you, it\'s easy and comfortable to be myself.</item>
        <item>You give confidence just by being there.</item>
        <item>You always know what needs to be done at the right moment.</item>
        <item>Your energy inspires success in others.</item>
        <item>You know how to support in the toughest moments.</item>
        <item>You\'re someone who always inspires to do more.</item>
        <item>You have a rare combination of strength and gentleness.</item>
        <item>With you, it\'s not scary to move forward.</item>
        <item>You\'re the embodiment of masculine wisdom.</item>
        <item>You know how to be sincere in any situation.</item>
        <item>Your confidence always inspires admiration.</item>
        <item>You\'re an example of how to be strong and kind at the same time.</item>
        <item>Your energy always creates an atmosphere of comfort.</item>
        <item>You always know how to make a moment special.</item>
        <item>Thank you for being in my life — with you, the world becomes brighter and more confident.</item>
        <item>I\'m grateful that I can count on you.</item>
        <item>Thank you for being here.</item>
        <item>Thank you for being mine.</item>
        <item>I\'m so grateful to fate that I met you.</item>
        <item>With you, I feel safe — thank you for your confidence and care.</item>
        <item>Thank you for your love and belief in me — you make this world better for me.</item>
        <item>I appreciate every moment spent with you — thank you for being in my life.</item>
        <item>Thank you for filling my life with meaning — you are truly a special person.</item>
        <item>I am happy to be close to someone like you — thank you for your love and care.</item>
        <item>You are incredibly strong: your determination and confidence inspire me and make me admire every one of your actions.</item>
        <item>You are like a reliable anchor that stabilizes me and brings confidence in the toughest moments.</item>
        <item>When you\'re around, I feel like I can overcome any obstacle — your support gives me strength and belief in myself!</item>
        <item>Your kindness and care are immeasurable, and that makes you a true man I can trust.</item>
        <item>You notice details that others might miss, and your attentiveness makes you unique in my eyes.</item>
        <item>Every conversation with you is a new experience, you take everything around you so easily and confidently, and I always learn something!</item>
        <item>You bring peace and confidence to any situation, like a support you can always rely on.</item>
        <item>You have the gift of listening and understanding, with you I always feel heard and valued.</item>
        <item>Your smile always warms me and reminds me that there is room for warmth and sincerity in life.</item>
        <item>With you by my side, I feel more confident, stronger, and full of ideas — your energy is contagious to everyone around.</item>
        <item>You are a combination of strength and masculine tenderness, and that makes you special in my eyes.</item>
        <item>You can see the merits even in simple things, and you make me see the world from a different angle.</item>
        <item>You are one of those people with whom you just want to sit in silence and enjoy the moment, you bring peace and serenity.</item>
        <item>You create an atmosphere of comfort and safety wherever you are, and that is a true gift to me.</item>
        <item>Every word you say is full of strength and meaning, and after talking to you, I always feel better and inspired.</item>
        <item>You are the embodiment of masculine confidence and kindness, and next to you, I want to be the best version of myself.</item>
        <item>Your confidence inspires me to reach new heights and achieve more with you.</item>
        <item>You bring confidence and calm into my life that cannot be faked — it\'s your true gift.</item>
        <item>Your support is invaluable to me: you are like a stone wall that I can always shelter behind and feel safe.</item>
        <item>You are incredibly wise, and your view of the world is always full of depth and meaning — I am always interested to learn your perspective.</item>
        <item>Next to you, there is always sincerity and reliability, things that are so lacking in everyday life.</item>
        <item>You know how to inspire, and that inspiration comes from your inner calmness — your confidence always commands respect.</item>
        <item>You are like the winter sun, bringing light and warmth even on the coldest days, it\'s always easier with you by my side.</item>
        <item>Time flies unnoticed with you, because every minute is filled with energy, joy, and meaning.</item>
        <item>You have a unique ability to establish real connections with people, and that is invaluable to me.</item>
        <item>Your kindness and care make this world better, and I am proud to know you and be close to you.</item>
        <item>You are one of those people who leaves a deep mark on the soul — your strength and wisdom mesmerize me.</item>
        <item>With you, I can talk about anything, and I always feel that our connection is special and meaningful.</item>
        <item>You embody masculine strength and intellect, and I often wonder how you manage to combine these qualities so harmoniously.</item>
        <item>You bring so much meaning and inspiration into my life that every day spent with you becomes an important event for me.</item>
        <item>Your smile is like a light in a dark tunnel, it always brings warmth and confidence when I need it.</item>
        <item>You have an incredible ability to create an atmosphere of confidence and comfort around you, which makes me calm next to you.</item>
        <item>Your energy fills me with positivity, and I never get tired of being around you — you are my source of inspiration.</item>
        <item>You know how to find light even in the simplest things, and that makes me believe in the best.</item>
        <item>You are an inspiration to many, and I am proud to be close to such an amazing person like you.</item>
        <item>Your belief in the best always inspires me to move forward despite all the difficulties, because with you, it\'s easier to do.</item>
        <item>You know how to give joy so sincerely that it cannot be ignored — it\'s always warm and fun with you.</item>
        <item>You remind me that everything is possible in life if you keep the faith and stay true to yourself, and with you, I become stronger too.</item>
        <item>Your generosity of soul knows no bounds, and I cherish every minute spent with you, it is priceless to me.</item>
        <item>You are a person who inspires belief in goodness and light in this world, and I am proud to be a part of your world.</item>
        <item>Your gaze fills my soul with warmth and calm — with you, I feel at ease.</item>
        <item>You have a rare gift of being sincere and open — this is a true treasure for me, I feel I can be myself with you.</item>
        <item>With you, I can dream about anything and not fear that dreams won\'t come true — with you, I believe in the future.</item>
        <item>You are like a guiding star, always leading me to the better, and I am not afraid to follow you.</item>
        <item>You are so beautiful not only on the outside but also on the inside, and that makes you truly amazing to me.</item>
        <item>Your words always support and inspire, and that is a true gift, for which I am grateful.</item>
        <item>You create an atmosphere of confidence and comfort even in the most ordinary situations, and I always feel at peace with you.</item>
        <item>You are always sincere and open, and I feel truly happy with you by my side — you are my source of joy.</item>
        <item>You know how to support and inspire, even when everything around seems confusing, you are always there, and I appreciate you for that.</item>
        <item>You are the brightest person I know, and this fills my life with joy and meaning, it is always easy with you.</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>